<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>oli m-c</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on oli m-c</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conditional forms with django</title>
      <link>/posts/conditional_forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/conditional_forms/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently begun some freelancing with a charity to help them out with some development work. They have a single django app that they use accross the business. Over the past couple of years, I&amp;rsquo;ve worked with django a lot, but always in the context of a DRF powered API and a separate front end. This application is a single monolithic application, using django as it was first designed, &amp;lsquo;batteries included&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 15:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapping park run courses</title>
      <link>/posts/mapping-park-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mapping-park-run/</guid>
      <description>I love park run. It&amp;rsquo;s been one of the main things I&amp;rsquo;ve missed during the last six, locked down, months. But one thing that&amp;rsquo;s always surprised me is the lack of rigourous information about the difficulty of various park run courses.
There are (or were, pre-pandemic) over 1,000 events UK events. But one event may have a multitude of different courses that are run each week. For example, my local park run Crystal Palace has at least two courses - a summer course that goes through muddy forest and a winter course that sticks to the paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple, simple, simple</title>
      <link>/posts/this_site/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/this_site/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to set up my own site for a while. Lockdown, longer nights, and a job search pushed me to actually do it. But I needed the barrier for setup to be as low as possible, but still give me a platform to grow and build it further. For now, i&amp;rsquo;ll concentrate on the writing - making it look good can come later.
This site is simple. I use the excellent Hugo to generate the html, and host it on github pages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>